(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
In a kingdom far far away where all nyut-nyut lives,
A sudden calamity strikes among the nyut-nyut who lives in harmony.
A pink giant monster has emerged out of nowhere and created havoc everywhere.
A lot of buildings and villages were destroyed.
All nyut-nyut were left hopeless until a mysterious magical squirrel arrived to find a legendary weapon, the Nut Blade.
The legend said that this mysterious squirrel will bring an end to this calamity...
強くなれる理由を知った
I've learned the reason why I can be strong
僕を連れて進め
Take me with you and move forward
泥だらけの走馬灯に酔う
Drunk on a mud-covered revolving lantern
こわばる心 震える手は
My stiffened heart, my trembling hands
掴みたいものがある
There is something I want to grasp
それだけさ
That's all
夜の匂いに
In the smell of night
(I'll spend all thirty nights) 空に睨んでも
(I'll spend all thirty nights) Even if I glare at the sky
(Staring into the sky) 変わっていけるのは自分自身だけ
(Staring into the sky) The only thing that can change is myself
それだけさ
That's all
強くなれる理由を知った 僕を連れて進め
I've learned the reason to become strong, take me and go forward
どうしたって 消せない夢も 止まれない今も
No matter what, a dream I can't erase, a present I can't stop
誰かのために強くなれるなら
If I can become strong for someone else
ありがとう 悲しみよ
Thank you, sadness
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
Beaten down by the world, I've learned the meaning of defeat
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ
Guren flower, bloom in glory
運命を照らして
Light up my fate
イナビカリの雑音が耳を刺す
The noise of lightning stabs my ears
戸惑う心 優しいだけじゃ守れないものがある
A confused heart, there are things that can't be protected just by being kind
わかってるけど
I know, but...
水面下で絡まる善悪 透けて見える偽善に天罰
Good and evil intertwined beneath the surface, divine punishment for the transparent hypocrisy
(Tell me why, tell me why, tell me why, tell me... I don't need you!)
逸材の華より 挑み続け咲いた一輪が美しい
More beautiful than a flower of rare talent, is the single flower that kept on challenging to bloom
乱暴に敷き詰められた 棘だらけの道も
Even a road roughly covered in thorns
本気の僕だけに現れるから
Will appear only to the serious me
乗り越えてみせるよ
I'll show you I can overcome it
簡単に片付けられた 守れなかった夢も
A dream easily pushed aside, a dream I couldn't protect
紅蓮の心臓に根を生やし
Rooted in a crimson heart
この血に宿って
Dwelling in this blood
ヒトシレズハカナイ チリユクケツマツ
An unknown, fleeting, fading end
ムジョウニヤブレタ ヒメイノカゼフク
A heartless, torn wind of screams blows
誰かの笑う影 誰かの泣き声
Someone's laughing shadow, someone's crying voice
誰もが幸せを願ってる
Everyone is wishing for happiness
どうしたって 消せない夢も 止まれない今も
No matter what, a dream I can't erase, a present I can't stop
誰かのために強くなれるなら
If I can become strong for someone else
ありがとう 悲しみよ
Thank you, sadness
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
Beaten down by the world, I've learned the meaning of defeat
紅蓮の華よ咲き誇れ
Guren flower, bloom in glory
運命を照らして
Light up my fate
Oh no!
Everything is burned down.
My house and the entire village is destroyed.
What is going on?
Are you alright?
A giant monster...
...burned down my entire village with its fire breath.
That is bad.
Do you know where that monster is heading?
I think it's headed to the next village.
Don't worry.
I shall take care of it for you so it won't destroy the other village too.
In order to do that, I need to collect power by singing and music.
So please, lend me your power, oh dear villager.
Oh, I will!
ライオン
Lion
星を廻せ 世界の真ん中で
Spin the stars in the center of the world
くしゃみすれば どこかの森で 蝶が乱舞
If you sneeze, butterflies dance in some forest
君が守る ドアの鍵 デタラメ
The key to the door you protect is a lie
恥ずかしいほど 窓際にならべあうよ
Lined up by the window, almost embarrassingly so
ライオンは強い
Lions are strong
生き残りたい 生き残りたい
I want to survive, I want to survive
まだ生きていたくなる
I still want to be alive
星座の導きで いま 見つめあった
Led by the constellations, we gazed at each other
生き残りたい 途方に暮れて
I want to survive, feeling lost
キラリ 枯れてゆく
Shining as I wither away
本気の身体見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true form
私 眠らない
I will not sleep
風はやがて 東へ向かうだろう
Soon the wind will head for the east
高気圧 この星の 氷河を溶かす
High pressure melts this planet's glaciers
誘い水を 飲んだ胸が熱い
My chest burns from the water that beckoned me
遠巻きな 物語
A distant story
かじりあう 骨の髄まで
Chewing on each other to the bone
生き残りたい 生き残りたい
I want to survive, I want to survive
まだ生きていたくなる
I still want to be alive
星座の導きで いま 見つめあった
Led by the constellations, we gazed at each other
生き残りたい 途方に暮れて
I want to survive, feeling lost
キラリ 枯れてゆく
Shining as I wither away
本気の身体見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true form
私 眠らない
I will not sleep
We shouted to survive!
何しに生まれたの
Why was I born?
何しにここにいる
Why am I here?
生き残りたい 埋まらない傷
I want to survive, with wounds that won't heal
光 恐れてた
I was afraid of the light
許された命が いま 惹かれあった
Now, these forgiven lives are drawn to each other
彷徨い果てて 君の隣で
After wandering aimlessly, by your side
ほてり 静めて
I'll cool my fever
本気の奏で見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true performance
私 眠らない
I will not sleep
生き残りたい 崖っぷちでいい
I want to survive, even if on the edge
君を愛してる
I love you
目覚めたいと 叫ぶ世界
The world screams that it wants to wake up
いま 惹かれあった
Now we are drawn to each other
狂気に変えて 祈り捧ぐよ
Turning it into madness, I offer my prayers
君を愛してる
I love you
星座の導きで
Led by the constellations
生き残りたい まだ生きていたい
I want to survive, I still want to be alive
君を愛してる
I love you
本気の心見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true heart
私 眠らない
I will not sleep
星が降る
Stars Fall
Lyrics: 桃木香織 (マツモトカオリ)
Music, Arrangement: JunbugP
Lyrics: Kaori Momoki
羽根もない この私が
I, who have no wings,
憧れてた あの空
gazed longingly at that sky.
背伸びして 星を掴む
Stretching on tiptoe to grab the stars,
真似をしてみた
I tried to imitate them.
負けないで 願いさえも
"Don't give up," even as the darkness
飲み込む闇 それでも
swallows even my wishes, nonetheless
手探りで 夢のカケラ
fumbling for the fragments of my dreams,
集めに行こう
I'll go to collect them.
ただグルグル回る車輪の中で
Just spinning 'round and 'round inside the wheel...
走っても走っても辿り着けなくて
No matter how much I run, I can't reach my destination...
先を行く君の背中ばかりを見ていた
I was only ever looking at your back as you forged ahead.
いつか超えられる
Someday, I'll be able to surpass you.
もっと強くなりたい
I want to become even stronger!
たった独り 生まれてきた
Having been born all alone,
その記憶も無くして
even that memory is lost.
泣き声も 届かないと
Lamenting that my cries
嘆いてみても
won't reach anyone...
信じていい 大きな木に
I can believe in the claw marks
しがみついた 爪痕
left from clinging to the great tree.
あの空へ 近付こうと
As a testament that
している証
I'm trying to get closer to that sky!
風が雲を流して
The wind sweeps the clouds away...
星が降る
Stars fall.
羽根もない この私が
I, who have no wings,
憧れてた あの空
gazed longingly at that sky.
背伸びして 星を掴む
Stretching on tiptoe to grab the stars,
真似をしてみた
I tried to imitate them.
負けないで 願いさえも
"Don't give up," even as the darkness
飲み込む闇 それでも
swallows even my wishes, nonetheless
手探りで 夢のカケラ
fumbling for the fragments of my dreams,
集めに行こう
I'll go to collect them.
Oh, I think after all this singing,
my power is still not enough to defeat the giant pink monster.
I heard you, young warrior.
I can help you with your worry.
As I, the keeper of the legendary weapon Nut Blade,
will lend you its power.
Is this... the voice of the Fireblade Priestess?
Yes, you are right.
I will lend you the power of this Nut Blade
if you can prove yourself that you have the spirit to fight the pink giant monster.
Hah! Okay!
Dragon Screamer
Lyrics: m.c.A.T, YUKINARI Music: 冨樫則彦
Lyrics: m.c.A.T, YUKINARI Music: Norihiko Togashi
Dragon Screamer!
胸に刻めよ 時代のリーダー
Carve it into your chest, the leader of the era
見た目より かなりコレは
This is quite something more than it looks
乾いた心 すさむよりは
Rather than letting your dry heart grow cold,
時に泣いて みてみれば
try crying sometimes
見えてくる明日 駆けるのは
What runs toward the tomorrow you can see,
紛れもなく 新しい自分
is unmistakably a new you
誰かのためでもなく
Not for anyone else,
ただもっと 上を目指せ
just aim for even higher
Dragon Screamer!
Wild and High! 昇る龍のようだ
Wild and High! Like a rising dragon
銀の光が 呼んだ未来が
The future called by the silver light,
導いた僕らを
guided us
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No question!
Dragon Screamer!
見えているのに はるかなゴールは
Even though it's visible, the distant goal
見た目より かなりにハーダー
is much harder than it looks
君が踏み出す 勇気持てば
If you have the courage to step forward,
やがて開く道が
the path will eventually open up
目指すべき場所 選ぶのは
Choosing the place to aim for,
紛れもなく 新しい自分
is unmistakably a new you
すべてを手にした 君は
You, who have everything in your hands,
どんな山をも 越える
will overcome any mountain
Dragon Screamer! Why do I? Why do I?
叫ぶ龍のようだ! Why do I? Why do I?
Like a screaming dragon! Why do I? Why do I?
銀の嵐が 吹き飛ばすんだ
The silver storm will blow away
迷いとか恐れを
hesitation and fear
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No question!
Oh My Way! 闇を抜け出したら
Oh my way! Once you escape the darkness,
つなげていく Climber
connecting climber
勝つ 優火勢 In the Case
The fire of victory in the case
気持ちハイペース ですでーす
Feeling high pace, desu-desu
果てしなく 止まらずに上目指せ
Endlessly, without stopping, aim high
諦めずに駆ける 時代のリーダー
Don't give up and run, leader of the era
いつまでも 変わらぬ夢ベクトル
The dream vector that never changes
空に浮かぶ ドラゴンさらい
A dragon sunrise floating in the sky
導き出す明日 世界はその手に
The tomorrow we bring out, the world is in your hands
Dragon Screamer! Why do I? Why do I?
昇る龍のようだ! Why do I? Why do I?
Like a rising dragon! Why do I? Why do I?
銀の光が 呼んだ未来が
The future called by the silver light,
導いた僕らを
guided us
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No question!
Dragon Screamer! Why do I? Why do I?
叫ぶ龍のようだ! Why do I? Why do I?
Like a screaming dragon! Why do I? Why do I?
銀の嵐が 吹き飛ばすんだ
The silver storm will blow away
迷いとか恐れを
hesitation and fear
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No question!
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No question!
You have proven me your spirit.
I shall bestow upon you the Nut Blade.
Thank you!
I shall use this weapon to defeat the monster.
Now I have the Nut Blade, I shall continue my journey
to defeat the giant pink monster.
If my hunch was right... I think...
I should go through the forest next.
Oh no! What happened to you, almighty dragon?
ピンクの巨獣にやられた。今は力が入らん。
I was beaten by a pink behemoth. I have no strength left.
翼も破壊されてしまった。
My wings have been destroyed as well.
Oh no, that is bad! I can help you recover if you can take me straight to the giant monster in exchange!
任せておけ。
Leave it to me.
おおかみは赤ずきんに恋をした
The Wolf Fell in Love with Little Red Riding Hood
偶然から始まる　必然のワンシーン
One scene of inevitability that begins from a chance encounter
遠くに見えたのは　揺れる赤色
What I saw in the distance was a swaying red color
不思議な森の奥で　見つけた黒い影
In the depths of the mysterious forest, I found a black shadow
何かが始まる予感　怖くて逃げ出した
A premonition that something is starting, I was scared and ran away
「出会い」は　終焉へ続く　シナリオ
An "encounter" is a scenario leading to the end
だからわざと　遠回りをした
So I purposely took a detour
会いたいなんて　触れたいなんて　話したいなんて　思わない
I don't think about wanting to meet, wanting to touch, or wanting to talk
かよわい君と　鋭い僕が　出会う　それが終わりさ
When frail you and sharp me meet, that's the end
残酷だって　罵ったって　運命は変わらない
Even if you call it cruel or revile it, fate will not change
ああ　どうして君が？　どうして僕が？　おおかみと赤ずきんなんだ
Ah, why are you? Why am I? The Wolf and Little Red Riding Hood
きっと君は今日も　この道を訪れる
Surely you will visit this road again today
そして僕は今日も　ずっと見守るしかできない
And I can do nothing but watch over you today as well
君はあの木の先で　いつも通り隠れてる
You are hiding beyond that tree, just like always
私は気づかぬふりしたまま　通り過ぎた
I passed by while pretending not to notice
視線は　交わらない　声は　届かない
Our gazes don't meet, our voices don't reach
ため息だけが　虚しく重なる
Only sighs overlap in vain
会えなくたって　触れなくたって　話せなくたって　いいから
It's okay even if we can't meet, can't touch, or can't talk
頼りない君と　ぎこちない僕が　そこにいるだけでいいんだ
It's enough just for frail you and awkward me to be there
これが恋だって　言わないなら　言葉なんてなくていい
If you won't call this love, then words aren't needed
考えたって　考えたって　エンディングは変わらない
No matter how much I think, the ending won't change
会いたかったんだ　触れたかったんだ　話したかった　本当は
I wanted to meet you, I wanted to touch you, I wanted to talk to you, truth be told
かわいい君と　優しい僕が　出会い　結ばれるエンド
An end where cute you and kind me meet and are tied together
何回だって　何回だって　神様に願ったよ
Time and time again, I prayed to God
でも　悲しいくらい　悲しいくらい　おおかみと赤ずきんなんだ
But, sadly, so sadly, we are the Wolf and Little Red Riding Hood
泣いている君を　慰めたくて　伸ばした腕が震える
Wanting to comfort you who are crying, my outstretched arm trembles
愛しているよ　抱きしめたいよ　だけど　できないんだよ
I love you, I want to hold you, but I can't
どうあがいたって　どう願ったって　爪も牙も消えない
No matter how I struggle, no matter how I pray, my claws and fangs won't disappear
だから　ただ待ってるよ　君の涙が止むまで　あの木の先で
So I'll just wait, until your tears stop, beyond that tree
Ah, here it is! If you eat this, you can recover super quick!
感謝する。
I'm grateful.
よし、完全復活だ。
Alright, I'm fully recovered.
今すぐ怪獣の元へ案内しよう。
I'll guide you to the monster right now.
Okay, let's go!
FLY HIGH!!
飛べ　FLY HIGH!!　汗と血と涙で
Fly, FLY HIGH!! With sweat, blood, and tears
...光る翼で
...with shining wings
今全部全部を蹴っ飛ばして Fly high!!
Now kick everything aside and Fly high!!
最果ての未来へ
Toward the furthest future
傷だらけの渡り鳥が
A migratory bird covered in wounds
空を睨んでる
Is staring at the sky
低空飛行する奴らが
Those flying at low altitude
笑おうと
May laugh
海の果てが見たい
But I want to see the edge of the ocean
心を無にして
Emptying my heart
向かい風に乗り
Riding the headwind
助走をつけて
Taking a running start
Hop step jumpで
With a hop, step, and jump
飛べ Fly high!!
Fly, Fly high!!
汗と血と涙で
With sweat, blood, and tears
光る翼が
The shining wings
君をどこへだって連れて行く
Will take you anywhere
青い衝動
Blue impulse
本能
Instinct
爪牙を剥き出しにして
Baring your claws and fangs
困難の旅路も
Even on a difficult journey
夢叶うまで
Until the dream comes true
何度だって飛べ Fly high!!
Fly again and again, Fly high!!
最果ての未来へ
Toward the furthest future
ぽつり降り出した雨が
The rain that started to fall
翼震わせる
Makes the wings tremble
行く手には黒い雲
There are black clouds ahead
今長い嵐の夜が来る
Now a long stormy night is coming
轟く雷鳴と
With the roaring thunder
砕ける波頭を
And the breaking crests of waves
飾りにして
Making them into ornaments
アンストッパブルで
Unstoppable
飛べ Fly high!!
Fly, Fly high!!
いつも胸の奥を
The fire that always
焦がす炎が
Burns deep in my chest
道を照らし出す灯台になる
Will become a lighthouse to light the way
夜明け前の
The battle
攻防が
Before dawn
才能の花咲かすから
Will make the flowers of talent bloom
命尽きるまで
Until life ends
限界を越え
Beyond the limits
最高速で飛べ Fly high!!
Fly at maximum speed, Fly high!!
飛べ Fly high!!
Fly, Fly high!!
汗と血と涙で
With sweat, blood, and tears
光る翼が
The shining wings
君をどこへだって連れて行く
Will take you anywhere
青い衝動
Blue impulse
本能
Instinct
爪牙を剥き出しにして
Baring your claws and fangs
全部全部を蹴っ飛ばして Fly high!!
Kick everything aside and Fly high!!
いつも胸の奥を
The fire that always
焦がす炎が
Burns deep in my chest
道を照らし出す灯台になる
Will become a lighthouse to light the way
夜明け前の
The battle
攻防が
Before dawn
才能の花咲かすから
Will make the flowers of talent bloom
命尽きるまで
Until life ends
限界を越え
Beyond the limits
最高速で飛べ Fly high!!
Fly at maximum speed, Fly high!!
最果ての未来へ
Toward the furthest future
It's over now, evil monster!
I have the high ground!
If I love you would you...
...utaraku kecil dahulu
...my little expression from before
MIR//or
Lyrics: Ayunda Risu / Music, Arrangement: フェリキタス (Feryquitous)
Lyrics: Ayunda Risu / Music, Arrangement: Feryquitous
The love will last, it will...
...selamanya ku kan peduli
...forever I will care
Write to me, broken thing have I become?
And you see love is there
Truly I have never had enough
Ordinary day, it seems the clouds of lies in the sky
Painted coloring my paradise
Titik hujan menghapuskan
Raindrops wash away
Segala luka duka emosi manusia
All the pain, sorrow, and human emotions
Siapa gerangan
Who exactly
Berkelana selamanya?
Is wandering forever?
Ah...
Will I love you like you love me too,
utaramu lebih dahulu?
your expression was first?
The love will last, it will...
...selamanya ku kan ada di sini
...forever I will be here
To me, enchanting have I become?
And you see love is there
Truly I will never have enough
Ordinary day, it seems the clouds of lies in the sky
Painted coloring my paradise
Titik hujan menghapuskan
Raindrops wash away
Segala luka duka emosi manusia
All the pain, sorrow, and human emotions
Rapuh dan terjerumus
Fragile and fallen,
Berkelana di dunia
Wandering the world
Ah...
The halo lingers on my ego
Why the light that radiates
Evaporates the scent in me as long as whispers follow me
Don't ever let go
Bahagia hanya menjadi hanya semata...
Happiness only becomes merely...
Ah...
To me, obsessive have I become?
And you see love is there
Truly I will never give it up
Ordinary, I will be the cloud
That color a rainbow
Start to show me my paradise
Titik hujan menghapuskan
Raindrops wash away
Segala luka duka emosi manusia
All the pain, sorrow, and human emotions
Rapuh dan terlarut
Fragile and dissolved,
Berkelana di dunia
Wandering the world
I finally realized to meet you...
utamakan untuk aku
prioritize it for me
Titik hujan membasuh bersih
Raindrops wash clean
Suka dan duka perasaan
The joy and sorrow of feelings
Dan melebur satu warna
And melting into one color
Yang bermakna
That is meaningful
Stop right there!
I'm here to stop you and release all the Nut-Nut from misery!
Wow! I can't believe that we've defeated the giant monster!
It's actually this cute! Aw!
As a celebration, let's sing one more song!
ひらひら　葉を落とす月
Fluttering, leaves falling in the moonlit night
夜明けが見たいって
Saying I want to see the dawn
叫んだ空
The sky I screamed at
ヒバリ
Hibari (Lark)
神様気取れの生まれ持った性
A natural disposition that can't act like a god
世界を愛して壊しました
I loved and destroyed the world
誰のもの？誰のもの？吾のもの？
Whose is it? Whose is it? Is it mine?
邪魔者は排除した
I eliminated the obstacles
管仲が何とか言ってたって
Even if Guan Zhong said something about it
エゴに掴まれて拒めないんだ
Being seized by ego, I can't refuse
まだ足りない　物足りない　死にたくない
Still not enough, unsatisfied, I don't want to die
機械仕掛けの腐った声で大人たちが云う
With mechanical, rotten voices, the adults say
うんざりだよ　心泥棒　愛してるわ
I'm fed up, you heart-thief, I love you
もうやめてよ
Stop it already
測って切って　売れば幸せですか？
Are you happy if you measure, cut, and sell it?
造られたショーケース　解け出した基盤
A fabricated showcase, a base that began to melt
世界　虚ろの果て
World, the end of the void
魂を一回　何処に隠した
Once, where did you hide your soul?
閑話休題　一服野
Digression, a field of rest
天つ乙女　歌と舞う
A heavenly maiden dances with songs
ヒバリの空
The sky of Hibari
輪廻転生　機械論　神格の論
Reincarnation, mechanism, the logic of divinity
人が人でなく落ちなくなる　地に言葉よ超え色の
Humans stop being humans and stop falling, words on earth transcend colors
宴を未来へ届けるよ　空から空へと繋げるよ
Delivering the feast to the future, connecting from sky to sky
限りなく泣くひばり達を遺す
Leaving behind the skylarks that cry endlessly
なんて本を聴かせてくれたっけ
What kind of book did you read to me?
メリディアン　二人のこと　愛してる
Meridian, the two of us, I love you
嘘でもいいから一度だけでも聴かせてよ
Even if it's a lie, just once, let me hear it
何処へ居て　何処で笑ってましたか？
Where were you and where were you laughing?
今は幸せですか？
Are you happy now?
置き去りのまま　届かない想い　ごめん
Left behind, feelings that don't reach, I'm sorry
何でやれなかったかな
Why couldn't I do it?
哀しい思い出は風に隠した
I hid the sad memories in the wind
歌よ　あなたの元まで
Song, reach all the way to you
天つ乙女　刻を舞う
A heavenly maiden dances with time
ヒバリの空
The sky of Hibari
独りでも笑ってゆけるんだわ
I can keep smiling even if I'm alone
独りでは生きてゆけないんだわ
I can't live on my own
ずっと拒んだり　愛したり
Always refusing or loving
裏で壊して　去れる姿　生きてゆく
Destroying from behind, I will live on in that departing form
測って切って　売れば幸せですか？
Are you happy if you measure, cut, and sell it?
造られたショーケース　もう逃げ出したい未来
A fabricated showcase, a future I want to escape from now
切り先の鍵
The key at the tip
魂を一回　何処に隠した
Once, where did you hide your soul?
閑話休題　一服野
Digression, a field of rest
天つ乙女　歌と舞う
A heavenly maiden dances with songs
夜明けを告げたら
If I announce the dawn
ヒバリの空
The sky of Hibari
Hi everyone!
Now, now, now...
How was my performance?
Do you like it?
Do you guys have fun?
And also,
for celebrating my victory
and my birthday,
we have special merch!
Yes!
So, here is the merch!
Birthday Set
Whoa! How cool is it?
And it's not only cool,
this year's merch was designed to be useful too.
So, let's have a closer look, shall we?
First up...
Ooh! Whoa!
It's an awesome A3 tapestry
drawn by natural sensei.
Whoa!
The whole illustration just... whoa,
it looks super awesome.
It looks so cool,
you can see that I'm holding my beloved...
Just look at that Warrior Risu
with full dark side.
Isn't it awesome?
Don't miss it!
And also, don't forget,
you guys gotta buy it, at least five, okay?
And I think, let's see what we have next.
Tumbler
Whoo! A super cute tumbler for everybody.
So you guys won't forget to hydrate.
Um, you can use it to drink water,
and you can use it pretty much always.
So be sure to use it every day, okay?
And next, we have this.
Squirrel Smartphone Ring
Whoa, a smartphone ring!
Ooh! So you can be super comfortable
and remember me when you're holding your phone.
And it also will secure your phone in your hand.
Very, very convenient.
And I think, let's see the full set now.
Whoo! Whoa, there's so much stuff actually.
And also, don't forget,
we have the full set purchase bonus here!
Set Purchase Bonus
So I will explain it a little bit.
For those of you who purchase the full set
will also receive a signed foil-stamped postcard.
And for my super Risuners
who purchase the limited edition full set
will receive a postcard autographed
by none other than me!
Autographed by me!
Isn't it awesome? Whoa!
And the pre-order window is only a month,
so make sure that you don't miss it.
Oh, oh, oh, also one more thing!
Did you guys listen to my new original song,
Hoshiga Furu?
It will be officially released after this stream
at midnight JST. JST, okay?
On my YouTube channel.
So go listen to it and,
um, maybe who knows that later
we will have MV for it? I don't know!
And last but not least,
for all of you who joined my membership,
you don't want to miss a special additional
3D performance in membership
just right after this show has ended.
If you haven't joined my membership yet,
do not hesitate
because the extra show is going to be mind-boggling!
What are you waiting for?
Join membership now! Whoo!
Whoa! Oops, um...
But I think the time is up. Oh...
And I have to continue,
but yes, I have to continue
with the membership show now.
So thank you so much everyone
for your support for this whole six years especially.
And thank you for celebrating my birthday
together with me.
So, bye-bye, Otsu-Arisu!
Thumbnail Illustrator: local catto / 3D Animation: OCTOLOID
Special thanks: 合同会社 VESSEL LIFE-, un., SAZA,
Special thanks: VESSEL LIFE- LLC, un., SAZA,
明日歌, sa-sara, raihiva, Toshiyuki, Koudai, 暁, ヨシくん。
Asuka, sa-sara, raihiva, Toshiyuki, Koudai, Akatsuki, Yoshi-kun.
- トライプロンティア合同会社 - 込山 武磨, synny
- Tri-Frontier LLC - Takuma Komiyama, synny
- 株式会社サウンド・シティ - 岡田 拓白, 志田 美千加, 小林 静彩, 椛倉 由紀
- Sound City Co., Ltd. - Takuhiro Okada, Michika Shida, Shizusa Kobayashi, Yuki Kabakura
Sound effects: - 有限会社データ・スリー・プロジェクト - 瀬子 裕一
Sound effects: - Data Three Project Co., Ltd. - Yuichi Seko
Planning: Ayunda Risu
Cinematography: カバー株式会社
Cinematography: Cover Corp.
General Direction: Ayunda Risu / カバー株式会社
General Direction: Ayunda Risu / Cover Corp.
Produced by: Ayunda Risu
Written and Directed by: Ayunda Risu
Ta-dah! Thank you! Mwah!
The Rise of the Nut Warrior